<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kharagpur Open Source Society</title>
    <link>/docs/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kharagpur Open Source Society</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/community/accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/community/accounts/</guid>
      <description>Accounts This document describes all the financial and accounting content related to KOSS. This particular function has to be carried out with the very high standards and utmost sincerity.
Why does KOSS require money? We conduct various workshops and events which require multiple costs like AV Cell booking, room booking, posters, domain hosting, servers, etc. To pay for the costs, the members had donated various sums of money to sustain the society while finding some self-funding source so as to continue the society in perpetuity without much financial strain on it’s individual members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/community/governance-review-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/community/governance-review-week/</guid>
      <description>Governance Review Week What is it? It is a week dedicated to the Governance of KOSS.
Our intention behind organizing the Governance Review Week is to help the core team members measure their level of involvement in KOSS. The week also promotes open discussions between Seniors and the Core team members. We want each one of our members to be frank with their batchmates as well as seniors in sharing their opinions and perspective on every aspect of KOSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/community/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/community/governance/</guid>
      <description>Governance Hierarchy  Executive Heads: The public face, managers and the decision makers. Rest -  Core Team Members: Freshers batch. (&amp;lt; 1 year of experience) Executive Members: Batchmates of Executive Heads. Advisors: People who have been an Executive member in the past and are still on the campus. Alumni: People who have graduated but were Executives when on campus.   Permanent membership of KOSS mandates serving one year as an Executive (either as Head or Member).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/community/onboarding-offboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/community/onboarding-offboarding/</guid>
      <description>Onboarding/Offboarding How to onboard someone in KOSS? See also Fresher&amp;rsquo;s Induction.
 Add them to the “Newbies” GitHub team. Add them to the Google Group. Check the delivery settings. Add them to the Slack. Add them to their batch’s private channel. Add their contact details on https://github.com/kossiitkgp/secrets Assign their 1:1 group Add their name to the website Add them to facebook groups (unofficial) Give access to KOSS’ facebook page Make them store numbers of everyone in team  How to re-designate Core Team Members as Executives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/community/one-on-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/community/one-on-one/</guid>
      <description>1:1  Pronounced as one on one
 During Freshers&amp;rsquo; Induction, every Core Team Member is assigned one (or more) Executive(s) as 1:1 mentor(s). The mentee and mentor(s) decide the frequency, length, time, venue and nature of their 1:1 meetups.
A 1:1 can be about * Career goals of Mentor/Mentee * Feedback/Discussion about involvement in KOSS * Brainstorming on new ideas/articles and implementations * Creating a comfort zone for new members to open up with the team</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>